ecsusa.com 2005-12-14

# Privacy Policy

About ECS > Privacy Policy 

ECS Elitegroup Computer Systems Inc. and its subsidiaries respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it. ECS Elitegroup Computer Systems Inc. provides this Privacy Statement to inform you of our Privacy Policy and practices and of the choices you can make about the way your information is collected online and how that information is used. We've structured our websites so that, in general, you can visit ECS Elitegroup Computer Systems Inc. on the Web without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. We make this notice readily available on our home page and at the bottom of every ECS Elitegroup Computer Systems Inc. Web page. 

**Types of information we collect and how we use them:** This Privacy Statement covers personal information, non-personal data collection 

  * **Personal information** is information that is associated with your name or personal identity. ECS uses personal information to understand better your needs and interests and to provide you with better service. Once you choose to provide us with personal information, you can be assured it will be used only to support your customer relationship with ECS. We take seriously the trust you place in us. ECS will not sell, rent or lease your personal information to others.

To personalize our websites, services or communications and improve our products and services, we may also ask you to provide us with information regarding your personal or professional interests, demographics, and experiences with our products or services. Providing this additional information is optional.

  * **Non-personal information** is data about usage and service operation that is not associated with a specific personal identity. ECS collects and analyzes non-personal information to evaluate how visitors use the ECS websites. 

Non-personal data we collect may include the pages visited on the ECS websites, unique URLs visited within www.ecsusa.com, browser type and IP address. Most non-personal data is collected via cookies or other analysis technologies. www.ecsusa.com Web pages use cookies and other technologies for data analysis and personalization services.

**Children's privacy**   
ECS Elitegroup Computer Systems Inc. is committed to protecting the privacy needs of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children's online activities and interests. ECS Elitegroup Computer Systems Inc. does not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13 and ECS Elitegroup Computer Systems Inc. does not target its websites to children under 13. 

**Will ECS Elitegroup Computer Systems Inc. disclose the information it collects to outside parties?**  
ECS Elitegroup Computer Systems Inc. will not sell, rent or lease your personal information to others. ECS Elitegroup Computer Systems Inc. will not share your personal information with third parties except in responding to your requests for products or services. Your permission will be requested when you submit your information. 

**How does ECS Elitegroup Computer Systems Inc. allow customers to update or change the information it collects?**   
ECS Elitegroup Computer Systems Inc. gives you the choice of receiving a variety of information that complements our products and services. You can subscribe to receive certain product- and service-specific information and ECS Elitegroup Computer Systems Inc. marketing communications. ECS Elitegroup Computer Systems Inc. communications may include new product information, special offers, or an invitation to participate in market research. We give you a choice regarding delivery of ECS Elitegroup Computer Systems Inc. communications by postal mail, e-mail and telephone. You may update or change your information by sending an e-mail to [info@ecsusa.com.](mailto:info@ecsusa.com). We will make every effort to honor your preferences. 

**Your consent**   
By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by ECS Elitegroup Computer Systems Inc.. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
